Hi, my name's Chance Platt from Humphries Archery here in American Fork, Utah.
Today we're talking about archery strategies, techniques.
We'll go over just a few of the techniques for improving your shot, making yourself a better shot when shooting.
Number one thing is...I believe...is probably the way that you're holding your bow. You want to make sure that you have a loose, but comfortable grip on your bow.
Number two is probably going to be in your stance.
So, I'll typically will have my feet about shoulder width apart.
Just so you're comfortable.
And then, when you draw your bow, you want to make sure that you can draw it smoothly.
There's no jerk....jerkiness to it.
And you want to make sure you have a good....good anchor point.
I'll rest...I'll rest my knuckles at my jaw every time.
My nose on the string.
And that way I can look down through my peep sight, and my sight.
And get the same site on the target every time.